Partial Guide to the I. Edward Kiev Papers, circa 1860 - circa 1980 K0001
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Pamphlets, circa 1860-circa 1970; K0001 Series 4; 18 linear feet (Box 14, Box 11, Box 16, Box 15, Box 10, Box 51, Box 9, Box 8, Box 7, Box 18, Box 45, Box 46, Box 49, Box 2, Box 1, Box 53, Box 52, Box 48, Box 6, Box 17, Box 5, Box 4, Box 3)
  - Agadat hapa'amon / Shir Ha-Leitsan, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 634)
  - Mechol ha-Roa = Shepherd's Dance, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 635)
    First festival of Israeli songs May 1960
  - Nochn streik: a komedie in 3 aktn, 1907 (Box 9, Folder 636)
  - [Hadlakat Nerot Shabbat - Kabbalat Shabbat - etsel Yehude Ashkenaz bi-mizrach Europah], 1900 - 1975 (Box 9, Folder 637)
  - Luah Yerushalyim lishnat 5703, 1943 - 1944 (Box 9, Folder 638)
  - History of Jews' College Library, 1860-1960 (Box 9, Folder 639)
  - Yediot la-Hevrah tenuat ha-Moshavim, 05/27/1975 - 05/29/1975 (Box 9, Folder 640)
  - ha-Ram Bam le-Am, 08/17/1949 (Box 9, Folder 642)
  - Seder Birkat ha-Mazon ve-Sheva Birakat le-Seudat ha-Nissuin shel Yonaton ve-Hanah Fefer, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 643)
  - Derakhim hadashot be-Heker ha-Helinizm ha Yehude, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 645)
    Reprint from "Tsiyon" v. 10: no.3/4
  - Madrikh ha-Telfon, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 646)
  - K. I (Kitve yad) Sefardi-Latino al hamavak neged ha-Talmud ba-tihilat ha-Meah ha-15, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 647)
  - ha-Sefer: shanah 1; kun.1, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 648)
  - ha-Sefer: shanah 3; kun 4-7, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 649)
  - "Olam ha-Ziknah" = Die Greisenwelt in Jerusalem: Alterversorgungshauses Moschab-Sekenim, 1903 - 1904 (Box 9, Folder 650)
  - Sihot, 1910 (Box 9, Folder 651)
  - Sh'ma: a journal of Jewish responsibility: 1/17, 10/08/1971 (Box 9, Folder 670)
  - Sh'ma: a journal of Jewish responsibility 4/80, 11/01/1974 (Box 9, Folder 671)
  - Hebrew Union College-Jewish Institute of Religion Bulletin: v. 9: no.3, 02/1957 (Box 9, Folder 672)
  - Erasmus Antiquariaat Boekhandel: Hebraica Judaica, 1900 - 1975 (Box 9, Folder 673)
  - Aan den Avond: Afscheidsrede; utgesproken te Ellecom op den 11 September 1921 door Ds. J. D. van Arkel (Box 9, Folder 674)
  - Antiquariaat Spinoza Amsterdam: Catalogue 2; Biblica, Judaica, Hebraica, 1900 - 1975 (Box 9, Folder 675)
  - Antiquariaat Spinoza Amsterdam: Catalogus 6; Biblia Hebraica, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 676)
  - Antiquariaat Spinoza: Catalogue 17; Ancient Israel, 04/1975 (Box 9, Folder 677)
  - Antiquariaat Spinoza: Catalogue 19 Judaica, 11/1975 (Box 9, Folder 678)
  - Hebraica, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 679)
  - Hebrew manuscripts in the Houghton Library of the Harvard College Library, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 680)
  - Society of Biblical Literature: One hundred sixth meeting - 1970- papers and abstracts (Box 9, Folder 681)
  - Sefer ha-Haluts (Hacholets), 1861 (Box 9, Folder 682)
  - Die Mainzer Thorahschreinvorhnge, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 683)
  - Sifrut: Contemporary Hebrew Literature, 1955 - 1957 (Box 9, Folder 684)
  - Bookplates: some examples by Edwin R. Schwabacher, 1909 (Box 9, Folder 685)
  - Haggadah shel Pessah be-otiyot gedulot, 1900 - 1975 (Box 9, Folder 686)
  - Ode to America = Aliekh Amerikah, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 687)
  - Judaism, 1900 - 1975 (Box 9, Folder 688)
    Missing title page.
  - Deuteronomy, 1800 - 1975 (Box 9, Folder 689)
  - Schletter'schen Buchhandlung H. Skutsch = Geschichte und deren Hilfswissenschaften: Antiquarischer Katalog Nr. 112, 1869 (Box 9, Folder 690)
    Bound with other catalogs.
  - Schletter'schen Buchhandlung H. Skutsch = Geschichte und deren Hilfswissenschaften: Antiquarischer Katalog Nr. 108, 1868 (Box 9, Folder 691)
  - Verzeichniss werthvoller Buecher aus dem Gebiete der Jdischen Literatur welche im Verlage der Schletter'schen Buchhandlung (H. Stutsch), 1867 (Box 9, Folder 692)
  - Bibliotheca hebraica et judaica: Verzeichniss von werken aus dem Gebiete der hebrischen, jdischen und orientalischen Literatur, 1870 (Box 9, Folder 693)
  - Schletter'schen Buchhandlung H. Skutsch = Geschichte und deren Hilfswissenschaften: Antiquarischer Katalog Nr. 121, 1871 (Box 9, Folder 694)
  - K. F. Khler's in Leipzig Antiquarische Anzeige-Hefte: no. 171, 1868 (Box 9, Folder 695)
  - Orientalia u. Sprachwissenschaft. Zum Theil Doubletten der Bibliothek des verstorbenen Professors Franz Bopp., 1868 (Box 9, Folder 696)
  - Catalogue of the Hebrew Union College Cincinnati, 1941 - 1942 (Box 10, Folder 697)
  - Bulletin of the General Theological Library ... Bibliography on Theology and Modern Literature: vol. XLIX: no. 4, 09/1957 (Box 10, Folder 698)
  - Spinoza's Mechanism, Attributes and Panpsychism, 05/1937 (Box 10, Folder 699)
    Reprint from the Philosophical Review, vol. XLVI
  - Minute Book of Congregations Zur Israel of Recife and Magen Abraham of Mauricia, Brazil, 03/1953 (Box 10, Folder 700)
    Reprinted from Publication of the American Jewish Historical Society; Vol. XLIII, No.3
  - The Jews of Charleston..., 12/1902 (Box 10, Folder 701)
    Inscribed on front page "Compliments of the author."
  - A Catechism of Religious and Moral Instruction for Children of the Hebrew Faith, 1890 (Box 10, Folder 702)
    Covers are detached, pages are brittle.
  - le-Toldot ha-Sugia, 1952 - 1953 (Box 10, Folder 703)
  - Das Judenthum in den Vereinigten Staaten von Nordamerika., 1881 (Box 10, Folder 704)
  - Die Staatsfeindlichkeit der jdischen Lehre, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 705)
  - De Joden in Nederland, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 706)
  - Samson Raphael Hirsch: in honor of the centenary of his birth, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 707)
  - Palestine, Zionism, Israel: catalogue 63, 1960 - 1975 (Box 10, Folder 708)
    Books from the libraries of Judge Neville Laski, and the late Israel Cohen and others
  - English & American Judaica: catalogue 64, 1960 - 1975 (Box 10, Folder 709)
  - Moses Mendelssohn-Ausstellung, 09/1929 (Box 10, Folder 710)
  - B. Kohen-Virgili: zamlbukh tsu zayn biografye un kharakteristik, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 711)
  - The mission of Judaism, its present day application: [report of the sixth international conference held in London, 1949.] (Box 10, Folder 712)
  - The Martyrs of Caesarea, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 713)
    Signed by author; "To Prof. Harry Slonimsky with compliments, S. L."
  - The defective in Jewish law and literature, 1916 (Box 10, Folder 714)
    a paper read before the New York Board of Jewish Ministers
  - Dem Sheiterhaufen Entgangen: dokumente, texte, photos jdischer Schriftsteller in den Jahren des deutschen Faschismus, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 715)
  - Semitic Studies in American Colleges, 1896 (Box 10, Folder 716)
    Reprinted from the Reform Advocate
  - Chaim Gross exhibition, 05/1953 - 07/1953 (Box 10, Folder 717)
  - Contemporary Art from Israel, 1948 - 1975 (Box 10, Folder 718)
  - Une Inscription Hebraque de 1144 a Bziers, 1878 (Box 10, Folder 719)
  - Oldest Tombstone-inscriptions of Philadelphia and Richmond, 1897 (Box 10, Folder 720)
  - A Hebrew University for Jerusalem, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 721)
  - Hebrew and homiletics, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 722)
  - Jewish art objects from the Collection of the Hebrew Union College Cincinati Art Museum 1947 (Box 10, Folder 723)
  - Guide to the Taylor-Schechter Genizah Collection, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 724)
  - Cultural Reconstruction of Russian Jewry, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 725)
  - Two American Jewish Pioneers of New Haven, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 726)
  - What are we Jews?, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 727)
  - Talmudic Forgeries: a case study in Anti-Jewish propaganda, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 728)
  - The Warsaw Ghetto Uprising, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 729)
  - Deutsche Literatur in hebrischer bersetzung, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 730)
    Reprint from Zeitschrift fur die Geschichte der Juden in Deutschlan: VI. Band
  - "Since Lincoln was in Illinois", 1939 (Box 10, Folder 731)
    Address delivered by Dr. Solomon B. Freehof, Rodef Shalom Congregation
  - "New Ghetto Walls", 1939 (Box 10, Folder 732)
  - On the Function of Religion in Culture, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 733)
  - Statehood and Zionism: what the Herut-Revisionist Movement stands for, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 734)
  - China-Israel, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 735)
  - The handsome young priest in the black gown; the personal world of Gershom Seixas, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 736)
  - The oldest Midrash: pre-Rabbinic ideals and teachings in the Passover Haggadah, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 737)
    Offprint: Harvard Theological Review. Vol. 31, no. 4 (Oct. 1938)
  - Analytic subject guide to the Jewish Quarterly Review covering the years 1889-1908, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 738)
  - Israel academy of sciences and humanities = ha-Akademiyah ha-Leumit ha-Isralit Le-Madeim, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 739)
  - Bibliography of the writings of professor Louis Ginzberg, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 740)
  - Selected List of the Writings of Gotthard Deutsch, Ph.D., 1916 (Box 10, Folder 741)
  - A tentative bibliography of Dr. Isaac M. Wise, 1917 (Box 10, Folder 742)
  - Bibliography of Dr. Samuel Hirsch (b. June 8, 1815; d. May 14, 1889), 1916 (Box 10, Folder 743)
  - Bibliography of the publications of Eric Werner, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 744)
  - Katalog der alten jdischen Kultusgegenstnde Gieldzinski-Stiftung in der Neuen Synagoge zu Danzig, 1904 (Box 10, Folder 745)
  - Rabbinic usage; examples for sentence structures in Rabbinic Hebrew, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 746)
  - Novellae on Tractate Baba Kamma by RaBaD of Posquieres, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 747)
  - Harvard University Library - Annual Report for the Year 1970-71, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 748)
  - Celebration on the occasion of the endowment of the Harry A. Wolfson Book Fund for Judaica in the Harvard College Library in honor of the eighty-fifth birthday, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 749)
  - The Jewish Museum under the auspices of The Jewish Theological Seminary of America ... Exhibits commemorating the tenth anniversary of the presentation of the Harry G. Friedman Collection ..., 1951 - 1952 (Box 10, Folder 750)
  - The Akedah, 1950 - 1975 (Box 10, Folder 751)
  - Haggadat Yehudah =The "Yahuda Haggada", 1955 (Box 10, Folder 752)
  - Tarukhat Zikron le-Heinrikh Feukhtvanger= Heinrich Feuchtwanger Memorial Exhibition, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 753)
  - The seventeenth Steinmetz Memorial Lecture, 05/1944 (Box 10, Folder 754)
  - Ganz TaNaKh (Torah, Neevim, Khetuvim) in Yudisher Ibersetsung, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 755)
  - B"H Luah Manhege Bet Ha-Kenesset (1964), 1964 - 1965 (Box 10, Folder 756)
  - Leaders' guide for Jewish survival in the world today, 1936 - 1939 (Box 10, Folder 757)
    Teachers guide to: Internal developments within Jewish communities
  - The Palestine railways tour time table and pocket guide, 1946 - 1947 (Box 10, Folder 758)
  - The pursuit of peace in the Middle East, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 759)
  - Migration and settlement, 07/12/1970 (Box 10, Folder 760)
  - The Conference on Jewish relations; a description of its organization, work and plans, 1942 - 1945 (Box 10, Folder 761)
  - Anglo-Jewish Art and History, Spring 1970 (Box 10, Folder 762)
  - Paralipomena Palstinensia: I. The oldest coins of JudaII. Stamped jar-handles of the post exilic age, 1900 - 1953 (Box 10, Folder 763)
  - Spinoza and the Enlightenment, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 764)
    Inscribed on cover by author: "To Ed a sagaeous and sincere and sedate friend a token of esteem, 3/9/53."
  - Would you be a rabbi?, 1950 - 1975 (Box 10, Folder 765)
  - Share chanukah with Jewish children around the world, undated (Box 10, Folder 766)
  - Festive manna, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 767)
  - The picture book of Pesach, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 768)
  - Seder ritual of rememberance, 1945 - 1975 (Box 10, Folder 769)
    For the six million Jews who perished at the hands of the nazis and for the heros of the ghetto uprisings
  - Consumer edition: Kosher products and services directory, 1967 - 1968 (Box 10, Folder 770)
  - Aslected bibliography in honor of Jewish Book Month, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 771)
  - A good year to you and yours, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 772)
  - Post-biblical Judaism: Its conception of Israel's place in the world, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 773)
  - Post-biblical Judaism: Its healthy mindedness, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 774)
  - Spinoza: an address delivered at the liberal Jewish Synagogue, London on Sunday March 13 th, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 775)
  - Judaism and the contemporary crisis in religion and society, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 776)
  - Dafe Ezer le-Madrikh, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 777)
  - Meetings of the Jewish Historical Society of England, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 778)
  - Judaism in action- manual for organization and programming, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 779)
  - Supplement shlosh regolim prayers, 1950 - 1975 (Box 10, Folder 780)
  - Alon tefilot: Oraciones e himnos para Rosh Hashana y Yom Kipur y para el Sbado, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 781)
    In Spanish
  - NCCJ what is the national conference of Christians and Jews, 1950 - 1975 (Box 10, Folder 782)
  - A Protestant platform of good will, 1950 - 1975 (Box 10, Folder 783)
  - A Jewish platform of goodwill, 1950 - 1975 (Box 10, Folder 784)
  - A Catholic platform of good will, 1950 - 1975 (Box 10, Folder 785)
  - Selected readings on Jews and Judaism, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 786)
  - Jewish history in the making, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 787)
  - How do we face change?, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 788)
  - Circumcision: brith or surgery?, 1950 - 1975 (Box 10, Folder 789)
  - The afikomon - or the broken matzo, 1950 - 1975 (Box 10, Folder 790)
  - Notes regarding Jewish libraries and museums, 1947 - 1948 (Box 10, Folder 791)
  - The Jewish year book, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 792)
  - The Women's Institute of Jewish studies: morning classes, 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 793)
  - Religion and morals: A short catechism for the use of Jewish youth, 1890 (Box 10, Folder 794)
  - The Seminary School of Jewish Studies ... evening classes for young people and adults, 1946 - 1947 (Box 10, Folder 795)
  - Ma-hu lanu mada ha-Mikra, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 796)
  - Sokratis u-mishanto: mi-tokh kitve Aplaton, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 797)
  - Birkat ha-Bonim be-Erev Yom ha-Kippurim, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 798)
  - Reshimat sefarim, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 799)
  - Sifriyah la-Am, 1969 - 1970 (Box 10, Folder 800)
  - The Unesco Public Library manifesto, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 801)
  - ha-Mavak ha-Midini shel ha-Yehudaim al zecuyotehem 1918-1933, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 802)
  - Lishkat ha-Sefarim, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 803)
  - Divarim al Prof. B. Z. Dinur, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 804)
  - Toldot Baal Arukh ha-Shalem, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 805)
  - Bcherliste 407 Neuerwerbungen Orientbuchhandlung Heinz Lafaire, 1952 - 1975 (Box 10, Folder 806)
  - Bcher-Verkaufs -Katalog 412: Philosophie, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 807)
  - The weathered wisdom of the wises, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 808)
  - Reform and Halakhah: the state of the art, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 809)
  - Keshet u-Magan, 1881 (Box 10, Folder 810)
  - Vehayu Yetedotov Emunah, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 811)
  - Palestineol. 4 no. 4 June-July 1947, 06/1947 (Box 10, Folder 812)
  - Palestine: vol 5, No. 4 Oct.-Nov. 1948, 09/1948 - 10/1948 (Box 10, Folder 813)
  - Palestine: Vol. 5, No. 5, Dec.1948-Jan.1949, 12/1948 - 01/1949 (Box 10, Folder 814)
  - Palestine: Vol. 6, No. 3: Fall 1949, 09/1949 (Box 10, Folder 815)
  - Congress bi-weekly: Vo. 26, no. 18, 11/30/1959 (Box 10, Folder 816)
  - Congress bi-weekly, 11/18/1963 (Box 10, Folder 817)
  - Congress bi-weekly: Vol. 38, No. 10, 10/29/1971 (Box 10, Folder 818)
  - Congress bi-weekly: Vol. 39, No. 6, 03/24/1972 (Box 10, Folder 819)
  - Sh'ma: a journal of Jewish responsibility: trial Issue 2, 06/09/1970 (Box 10, Folder 820)
  - Sh'ma: a journal of Jewish responsibility: trial Issue 1, 05/22/1970 (Box 10, Folder 821)
  - Sh'ma: a Journal of Jewish responsibility: 2/34, 06/02/1972 (Box 10, Folder 822)
  - West London Synagogue review: issue No. 6, 03/1968 (Box 10, Folder 823)
  - Sh'ma: a journal of Jewish responsibility: 1/14, 05/14/1971 (Box 10, Folder 824)
  - The Synagogue review: Vol. 39, no. 1, 09/1964 (Box 10, Folder 825)
  - Pointer; quarterly Journal of the Union of Liberal and Progressive Synagogues, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 826)
  - Jewish daily bulletin, 08/21/1927 (Box 11, Folder 827)
  - Jewish daily bulletin, 08/22/1927 (Box 11, Folder 828)
  - Jewish daily bulletin, 08/23/1927 (Box 11, Folder 829)
  - Jewish daily bulletin, 08/25/1927 (Box 11, Folder 830)
  - Dimension: vol. 1; no. 3, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 831)
  - Dimensions in American Judaism; Vol. 2; no. 2, 1967 - 1968 (Box 11, Folder 832)
    Formed by the union of the periodicals, Dimension and American Judaism
  - Dimensions in American Judaism: Vol. 2; no. 3, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 833)
  - Dimensions in American Judaism: Vol. 2, No. 4, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 834)
    Official publication of the Union of American Hebrew Congregations in cooperation with the National Federation of Temple Sisterhoods
  - Dimensions in American Judaism: Vol. 4, No. 3, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 835)
  - Dimensions in American Judaism: Vol. 5, No. 3, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 836)
    Official publication of the Union of American Hebrew Congregations in cooperation with the National Federation of Temple Sisterhood
  - The JPS bookmark, 09/1957 (Box 11, Folder 837)
  - The JPS bookmark: Vol. 6, no. 3, 09/1959 (Box 11, Folder 838)
  - The JPS bookmark: Vol. 6, no. 4, 12/1959 (Box 11, Folder 839)
  - The JPS bookmark: Vol. 8, no. 2, 06/1961 (Box 11, Folder 840)
  - The JPS bookmark: Vol. 13, no. 2, 06/1966 (Box 11, Folder 841)
  - The JPS bookmark: Vol. 15, no. 4, 12/1968 (Box 11, Folder 842)
  - Et lishhok=Humor in Talmud und Midrasch, 1914 (Box 11, Folder 843)
  - Toldot ha-Minut ba-Tekufah Sadia, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 844)
  - Keles Killusin, 1927 - 1950 (Box 11, Folder 845)
  - Kadmoniyot ha-Yehudim be-Eropah: ha-hayim ha-politiyim (me-hathalet yeme ha-benayim ad masa ha-tselav), 1939 (Box 11, Folder 846)
  - On seeing Sargent's "Synagogue" and "Church", 11/07/1919 (Box 11, Folder 847)
    reprinted from the "American Hebrew"
  - Hebrew Union College bulletin: vol. 6, no. 4, 05/1947 (Box 11, Folder 848)
  - Hebrew Union College-Jewish Institute of Religion Bulletin: vol. 9, no. 3, 02/1957 (Box 11, Folder 849)
  - Hebrew Union College-Jewish Institute of Religion Reporter, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 850)
  - Ha-Sefer ha-Ivri 1914-1924 (Box 11, Folder 851)
  - Die Poesie der Juden im Mittelalter, 1907 (Box 11, Folder 852)
  - Heidenischer ursprung des Brauches zwischen Passah- und Wochenfest nicht zu heirathen, 1869 (Box 11, Folder 853)
  - Apercus preliminaires sur les manuscrits de la mer Morte, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 854)
  - Mikraot: pirk?e-keriah le-mitlamdim ule-vate-sefer: leket mi-tokh ha-Musaf ha-Ivri shel ha-Yudisheh Rundshoy, 695-696, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 855)
    Text in Hebrew; glosses in German
  - Das Alte Testament und seine Erfllung im Christentum, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 856)
  - Small holding and irrigation: the new form of settlement in Palestine, 1920 (Box 11, Folder 857)
  - State of Israel: birth and growth, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 858)
    Reprinted from Israel and the Middle East
  - Funem Humesh -Sifre Mikra - fartaytsht yudish, 1913 - 1914 (Box 11, Folder 859)
  - Luah Ivri Taytsh, 1924 - 1925 (Box 11, Folder 860)
  - Through truth to Peace: a pamphlet issued by movement for "Peace with Israel", 1952 (Box 11, Folder 861)
  - Disertatsiah al R. Yitzhak Elhanan, 1961 - 1962 (Box 11, Folder 862)
  - The mood of the Talmud and the great Talmudic dictionary, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 908)
    Union anniversary series
  - Corrections and addenda to annotated bibliography - Jewish education in Europe, 1914-1962, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 909)
  - Beauty in holiness, 10/1956 (Box 11, Folder 910)
  - Olim (Alim) meassef le-inyuni ha-Sefah ve-Tarbut, 1912 (Box 11, Folder 911)
  - The Jewish National and University Library and the Graduate School, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 912)
  - "As it goes with Israel, so will it go with us", 1968 (Box 11, Folder 913)
  - Dibrey Hephetez (Divre Hefets)="Acceptable Words " on extracts from various unprinted works of eminent Hebrew Authors, 1853 (Box 11, Folder 914)
  - Di lehre fun Leben (di fiziologie) bearbaytet nokh Lunkevitsh un andere durkh D. Mardfin [un Dr. Haysin], 1897 - 1898 (Box 11, Folder 915)
  - Lemaan Hayeled Vehanoar: Legal problems concerning the placing of children in families, 01/1946 (Box 11, Folder 916)
  - Di Nutslikher hand-bukh - Emanual, Got iz mit unz, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 917)
  - Zikhronot le-ven Yerushalayim 594-678, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 918)
    Original copy is 208 pages, library has only the first 18 pages.
  - Maimonides Commentar zum Tractat Bezah, 1898 (Box 11, Folder 919)
    In German, Arabic and Hebrew.
  - Sprawozdanie instytutu nauk Judaistycznych w Warszawie, 1929 - 1930 (Box 11, Folder 920)
    Very brittle.
  - Matsav Yerushalayim-Mazaw Jerusalam, 1882 (Box 11, Folder 921)
  - ha-Nasi bi-sanhedrin ha-Gdolah, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 922)
    brittle. Covers falling off.
  - Kitve Yehezkel Kaufmann, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 923)
  - Histagelutam shel olui Temim le-tanai Yerushlayim, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 924)
  - The Jewish library in school, center and synagogue, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 925)
  - Sarid mi-pirush ha-RamBamli-Gm(gemara) Shabbat el pi ktav yad 2. mafteah le-Igrot ha-RamBam, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 926)
  - Me-artsenu: kovets sefirot hakirot ve-teurim mi-shenat 1922-1923 (Box 11, Folder 927)
  - Likutim mi-tokh ha "Hikdamah" shel Ibn Haldon, undated (Box 11, Folder 928)
    Text in Hebrew and Arabic
  - Scopus: Vol. 19, no. 2, 06/1965 (Box 11, Folder 929)
    Special fortieth anniversary number
  - Building on strength; the program for the Harvard University Center for Jewish Studies, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 930)
  - Promoting School Enrollment - Media Information Manual, 1960 - 1975 (Box 11, Folder 931)
  - Chasidic Tales Retold materials: Teacher's Handbook and A Collection of Fifteen Articles, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 932)
  - teacher's Handbook ...Certain people of the Book, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 933)
  - General Survey of the Dead Sea and Ein Bokek region from the historical aspect position of the hotel, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 934)
  - Officers and Board Members of the National Jewish welfare Noard - Thumbnail sketches, 1974 - 1975 (Box 11, Folder 935)
  - Hebrew Union College - Jewish Institute of Religion Faculty Bulletin: Vo. 4, no. 4, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 936)
  - Israel and the diaspora: a new look, 03/1974 (Box 11, Folder 937)
  - The Jewish National University Library: report on the activities in the year 1970, 03/1971 (Box 11, Folder 938)
  - Mission to Israel: the disposition of informational media guaranty funds in Israel for education, science, culture and humanities, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 939)
  - The Jewish Museum, 10/1933 (Box 11, Folder 940)
  - Yizkor books: new library-bound reprints of memorial volumes commemorating Jewish communities destroyed in the Holocaust: from the collections of the New York Public Library and the National Yiddish Book Center, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 941)
  - Sheluhot: hov. 44, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 942)
  - Stamps = Bulim, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 943)
  - Kiryat Ono le-ezrah, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 944)
  - Bat Kol; Israel music journal, no. 1, 01/1961 (Box 11, Folder 945)
  - Bat Kol; israel music journal, no 2, 03/1961 (Box 11, Folder 946)
  - Bat Kol: et ktav le-musikah, no 1, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 947)
  - Bat Kol: et ktav le-musikah: hov. 2, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 949)
  - Bat Kol: ktav et le-musikah: hov. 4, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 950)
  - Bat Kol: ktav et le-musikah, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 951)
  - ha-Matsil ha-Hovov ba-Yam, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 952)
  - American Friends of the Hebrew University Bulletin, 12/1957 (Box 11, Folder 953)
  - Livres Anciens & Modernes: Jacques Levy: Catalogue no. 219, 1950 - 1975 (Box 11, Folder 954)
  - Livres Anciens & Modernes: Jacques Levy: Catalogue no. 222, 1950 - 1975 (Box 11, Folder 955)
  - Livres Anciens & Modernes: Jacques Levy: Catalogue no. 227, 1950 - 1975 (Box 11, Folder 956)